http://www.thecontractorsgroup.com/privacy_policy.htm

I'm in the middle of combining 4 websites and so occasionally the links will take you back and forth until I've finished it. I'm very sorry for the inconvenience but when it's done it'll be great!
HOME
SITE MAP
WHO WE ARE
NEWSLETTERS
SEARCH:
a separate window to another of my websites will open where you can search ALL of my construction info at once - look near the top when you get there
FOR
CONTRACTORS
GO
STRAIGHT TO OUR YAHOO STORE WHERE YOU CAN PURCHASE AND DOWNLOAD
FILL-IN-ABLE CONSTRUCTION CONTRACT FORMS
GET
MORE INFO ABOUT OUR DOWNLOADABLE FILL-IN-ABLE CONSTRUCTION CONTRACT FORMS
FORMS
FAQ's
FREE
CONSTRUCTION
MAGAZINES
ARTICLES
AND TUTORIALS
CONSTRUCTION LIABILITY INSURANCE AND SURETY BONDS FOR CALIFORNIA
'FACTOR' YOUR INVOICES
CONTRACTOR
LICENSE STUDY GUIDES!
DEDUCT
YOUR HEALTH EXPENSES 100%
SUBSCRIBE
TO OUR FREE NEWSLETTER
AIA FORMS INFO
This website is not associated with the AIA in any way. Downloadable AIA forms are available only through the AIA.
A101
A105
A107
A141
A142
A201
A205
A305
DISCLOSURE
By Contractors For Contractors!
Our
Privacy Policy
We do not collect any information that is not freely and knowingly
provided by you when and if you fill in any of our forms.
And when and if you do fill in any of our forms, to the extent permitted by law, your information is kept private
and confidential and is NOT, and will NEVER be,
sold nor distributed in any way.
This means that your information stays private,
period.
I am an Internet consumer myself and spam/uce really bugs me.
The worst is when I get an email that states "You are receiving
this email because you subscribed to ... " when I know
I did NOT subscribe. errgghh!
I used to list my home number here for folks to call me but due
to our
son's severe health problems I can no longer do that. So please
email me if
you'd like to chat about it.
Per California Spam Laws I have to state the date that our privacy
policy goes/went into effect. Our privacy policy went into effect
January 2000 when we first started our site. :)
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
The most important thing to realize here is, again, we do not collect any personal information from you unless you fill in one of our forms, and when and if you fill in any of our forms we do not distribute that information to anyone in any way.
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a strictly voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected only if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites.
They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic.
They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.
We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.
Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to Download-Construction-Forms.com and TheContractorsGroup.com and store.Construction-Business-Forms.com Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
The most important thing for you to know is that we will never distribute your personal information.
Your privacy is as important to us as our privacy is.
Free Gift - Practical Solutions, Higher Incomes, and Less Hassles! Click here (a separate window will open) to get the free gift I have for you at InformedContractors.com. Thank you!
HOME | WHO
WE ARE | OUR
FORMS DOWNLOAD YAHOO STORE | FORMS
FAQ's | HONEST CUSTOMER OR DEADBEAT CHEAT?? | CONSTRUCTION SURETY BONDS CALIFORNIA | AIA
FILL 'EM IN EMPLOYER FORMS | EMPLOYMENT SCREENING BACKGROUND CHECKS | DEDUCT
Any part or portion or section of this website may be copied
or reproduced in any manner as long as I am given full credit and a working
link back to this site. When using forms obtained from this site, please
do not remove the copyright information at the bottom, unless and until
you receive explicit written permission to do so.
Disclaimer: While every attempt has been and will be made
to keep the information at this website accurate and up-to-date, we do
not represent ourselves as experts. Even though we have used some and/or all
of the forms and methods posted here, we do not guarantee that these
forms
and/or methods are acceptable for your situation(s). For specific legal
questions and/or expert assistance we suggest that you contact an attorney.
I may not be able to answer the phone)
All Rights Reserved,
exclusive of U.S. Government Works
Please
click here for our privacy policy
